SPECIAL OFFER: -35% | TIME LEFT:

### Language

Free Remote Desktop Software
============================

Remote Desktop Connection over Internet
=======================================

Alternative short domain [900100.net](https://900100.net/)

  English

* * *

Privacy Statement
-----------------

* * *

### General

Your privacy is very important to us at AeroAdmin. Because of that, we strictly follow all legal requirements and exercise care when it comes to collecting, processing, using, and disclosing your information and data. The purpose of this statement is to provide an overview of your rights when using our website and software, as well as explain what data we collect and why we do so.

### Personal Data

The term “personal data” encompasses any information related to an identified or identifiable individual. Examples of personal data include your name, address or mailing address, and phone number. If your name is included in your email address, your email address would also fall under the category of personal data. On the other hand, information that cannot be used to identify an individual does not fall under the category of personal data; examples of such information include your body size, gender, age, and education.

### Use and Disclosure of Data

We may collect your personal data through automatic or manual means. Any personal data that we collect from you will only be used to respond to inquiries from you, to process contracts with you, or for our internal administration purposes.

We will not disclose your personal data unless required by one of the following specific circumstances:

* To process a payment with the payment provider or other relevant third party
* You have expressly consented to the disclosure of your data
* We are required by law to disclose your data (e.g., in response to a subpoena or court or administrative order)

We will never sell your data.

### Deletion of Data

You may revoke your consent to the storage of your personal data at any time. We will delete your personal data when you revoke your consent and after storage of your data is no longer necessary for us to process contracts. Regardless of whether you expressly revoke your consent, we will delete your personal data if its storage becomes prohibited by law or if we no longer need it to provide our services.

### Website

In order to protect your privacy, when using our website we encourage you to only provide us with the data that is necessary for us to meet your needs and/or to assist in improving the quality of our services to you. However, you should be aware that we do automatically collect some data for statistical analysis purposes.

### Access Protocol

We log basic information related to every visit to our website and related resources. This is done for internal statistical analysis purposes and to help us ensure data security. In order for us to meet our analysis and security needs, we collect and store some information from your web browser and computer, including the following:

* Operating system
* Browser type and version
* Previously visited website
* Hostname of the machine and IP address
* Time of the server inquiry

### Emails and Newsletters

If you sign up to receive our newsletter or use the email services offered through our website, we will store your email address. In order for us to ensure that you are the owner of the email address and/or that the owner agrees to receive our newsletter, we may gather additional information from you. You may revoke your consent to the storage and use of your email address to deliver our newsletter and any other additional information gathered for this purpose at any time.

You may also unsubscribe from our email newsletter at any time.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small text file sent from a website that can be stored on visitor’s computer or by the visitor’s web browser. When a visitor uses that same computer or browser to return to the website, the information in the cookie file is sent back to the website’s server. Although enabling the use of cookies serves a purpose and ensures maximum functionality when using our website, it is possible to use our website with cookies disabled.

To protect your privacy, we avoid the overuse of cookies and only utilize them for the following purposes:

* Managing different user sessions (session tracking)
* Storing user settings for our website (e.g. language)
* Web analytics

### Web Analytics Tools

Our website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how visitors use our website. The cookie will generate information about your use of our website, including your IP address, and this information will be transmitted to and stored by Google on its servers in the United States. Google will then use this information so that it can evaluate visitors’ activity on our website so that it can generate statistical reports for us; Google also uses this information to improve its services related to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer information that it collects to third parties if required by law or if third parties process the information on Google’s behalf; however, Google will not associate your IP address with any other information it stores. If you choose, you may disable the use of cookies related to Google Analytics through your web browser’s settings; however, doing so may negatively impact the functionality of some features on our website. By using our website, you are giving your consent to Google to process and store your data as explained in this paragraph.

If you wish to prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the [Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on developed by Google here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

### Software

AeroAdmin will automatically collect some data in order to ensure reliable and safe operation of the software, to enable some advanced features, and to assist in developing future product improvements. The data automatically collected includes the following:

* Time the program is launched
* IPaddress
* Statistical information about your computer (e.g., CPU, MAC address, HDD Serial, Screen Resolution)
* Time and duration of AeroAdmin sessions and AeroAdmin IDs of participants

### Changes

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement in compliance with the relevant legal requirements at any time.

### Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy, please contact us via the means listed [here at AeroAdmin Support Center](https://www.aeroadmin.com/en/support.html). You can contact us to determine whether any of your data is stored by us and, if so, what specific data is being stored; additionally, you can send us requests to remove or correct your data. We also welcome any suggestions you may have.

* * *

START WORKING WITH AEROADMIN RIGHT NOW
--------------------------------------

### IT'S [FREE](https://www.aeroadmin.com/en/buy.html#full-license-comparison) FOR PERSONAL AND BUSINESS USE

Choose Language

  English

* * *

* * *

Copyright © AeroAdmin LLC. All rights reserved.  |  POB 59571, San Jose, CA 95159, US  |   [EULA](https://www.aeroadmin.com/en/eula.html)  |   [Privacy Statement](https://www.aeroadmin.com/en/privacy_policy.html)
